rachel greene

email: greenest@gmail.com portfolio: www.rachelgreenedesign.com linkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/greenerachel

about me

I am a UX Designer who thinks of myself as a generalist. My motivation is to understand people and how they interact with the world. As an Architect, I learned to see the big picture and think outside of the box. I now use this knowledge to create User Experiences that are thoughtful, elegant and delightful to use.

tools

Sketch3, Axure, Invision, POP, Omnigraffle, Balsamiq, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, CSS, HTML5, Revit, AutoCAD, SketchUp, Paper and Pen

skills

Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristic Evaluations, Communication, Leadership

languages

English (native), Spanish

education

User Experience Immersive

General Assembly Seattle, Washington

UX Design

Career Foundry Online

Master of Architecture BS Architecture

Washington State University Pullman Washington

fun fact

- 1. I'm Architect 10779 in the State of Washington.
- 2. I spend my free time with my husband and daughter.
- 3. I've only lived in 2 states but 4 countries

select projects

Fair Weather Camper

Web Application

skills: Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristics

tools: Sketch3, Invision, Sketching

Festival Application

Mobile Application

skills: Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristics,

Communication

tools: Axure, Sketching

RGDesign

Portfolio Website

skills: Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristics

tools: Sketching, sketch, HTML5, CSS

Epilog

Desktop Application

skills: Research, Wireframes, Heuristics, Communication

tools: Sketch3, Invision, Sketching

experience

UX Designer Sept 2015- Dec 2015

General Assembly

UX Designer Aug 2014 - Sept 2015

Freelance Designer

Architect Aug 2012- May 2014

Boxwood

Project Designer Aug 2010 - Aug 2012

Stock & Associates

Project Designer April 2008 - May 2009

Jones & Jones

Project Designer Nov 2007- April 2008

PB Architects

Municipal Development Volunteer June 2005 - July 2007

Peace Corps El Salvador